{
    "id": "4102080828284fae8d6fe2abf8f52cac",
    "title": "For, Since, From, In",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a27fc0d83c3c4567bc0714871ea51a87",
            "title": "For, Since, In, From",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I once studied classical music …………… about two years.",
                    "description": "Use for with a period of time.",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since",
                        "from",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am going to Switzerland ………….. the summer.",
                    "description": "Use for with a period of time.",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "from",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will be in Singapore ……………. the next ten days.",
                    "description": "Use for with a period of time.",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have known each other …………… our school days.",
                    "description": "Use since with the starting point.",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "from",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have known each other …………… a long time.",
                    "description": "We use for with duration. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since",
                        "from",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was the worst disaster ………….. decades.",
                    "description": "We can use in to talk about duration. This is particularly common after negatives and superlatives. For is also possible here.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "for",
                        "from",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has been a go-getter …………… her earliest childhood.",
                    "description": "With perfect tenses, since and for are more common.",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "from",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………….. now on, I am going to be punctual.",
                    "description": "We use from with the starting point. The difference between from and since is that since is mainly used with perfect tenses.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Since",
                        "From",
                        "For"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I work ……………… dawn to dusk.",
                    "description": "We use from with the starting point. It is mainly used with simple tenses. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "from",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………….. his earliest childhood, he hated cats.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "From",
                        "Since",
                        "For"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will be home …………. Monday on.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "from",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………….. the dawn of civilization, people have made wars.",
                    "description": "We can use 'from' in expressions that mean right from the start. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "From",
                        "Since",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}